We fell through to the subway.
Yeah.
Where are the others?
I don't think they fell with us, but the corporal here has banged up pretty badly.
We need to get him to the temporary shelter above ground.
There should be medics there who can treat his wounds.
Hey! Idiot! You down there?
I can hear you! You okay?
Yeah, of course we are!
There's no way we die in a place like this, dumbass.
Hey, can you guys get out?
Yeah, no problem.
Then you guys go ahead and we'll catch up with you.
We've got to find a med team for the corporal.
We'll meet you at the defensive line.
Wait, shouldn't we...
Kay, see you at the line!
All right.
We'll try to get out.
We'll monitor your Recissor.
We'll hoowie.
Now we can get out there with them.
We'll catch up on our Trunet.
See, we'll be in the next in the meantime.
We'll be back in the next one.
We'll catch up with you at top.
Little Man.
There's no new trick.
We'll catch up on both sides.
We'll discuss here tonight.
I'm looking at how hard that's with us.
We'll take it on both sides.
There's no отнош anywhere we can.
Tea happens to run by the marker.
She won't be Sig.
All right.
T impossireat!
Where's it?
Well, damn it. I didn't kill the commander, after all.
Impressive. That attack took out a whole squadron of our men. It looks like the humans are sending in their strongest forces.
Strongest forces?
These soldiers are with the Vampire Extermination Unit's most elite squad, the Moon Demon Company.
All right, everyone.
Are you ready to end this war once and for all?
Then let's slaughter the livestock. Full-blown extermination.
Let me ask you something. Do you really like the taste of human blood? Or is this a twisted reenactment of the Last Supper?
Lend me your power, Demon Blade Mahi Runoyo.
Don't hold back. This is the fight that you've been training for. Protect this line. Kill every one of them.
I don't want nobody to get killed. I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight.
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread. Always don't take all of the weight. You always do.
There will always be something you cannot control. We will overcome. Your salvation has begun.
No sun, no light, such a mess all over. Don't kill your walls. You make me realize who I need.
I'll be there, hold on, the changes somehow. So where are you now?
She嗨.
I'll reach you might of the shadows of the earth. Illusions apart.
Your fallen angels's wrong, what they'll know is the pain of me. I assume for me.
And after all, don't MID TOEVE EARTH Akểnicka
Come on, Slowpokes. It's time to go.
Okay.
We're heading out, so you guys hold down the fort, all right?
Sure. Have fun.
Bye-bye. See you later.
Lunchtime is my favorite time of day.
So hungry.
My stomach's rumbling.
Careful now. You're gonna trip over someone if you rush like that.
Hey, you. What's up?
Can't you see that I'm reading?
Oh, come on. Take a break for a sec.
What is with you? You're being annoying.
If we could escape from this place, what would you want to do?
Where would you want to go?
Huh? Did you hit your head or something?
Listen, we can't escape because the virus would kill us as soon as we got outside.
Use your imagination.
If we could escape to the outside with the rest of the family.
If we could go to a place without any vampires, then don't you think we would have fun?
Without vampires?
Yeah. Just us family.
Sure, that sounds great, but it's impossible.
You'd be happy?
Yeah, of course I would.
Then I guess I'd better get busy working on that.
On what?
Mm-mm. It's a secret.
Well, I've got some errands I need to run.
Errands?
What do you have to do?
If I told you, it'd ruin the surprise.
What a weirdo.
Unfortunately, Mika didn't escape the way he thought he would.
And it turned out the world beyond was no paradise.
We should go meet the others.
But the corporal...
He'll be fine here. The doctors say he's going to recover.
That's good. I'm glad.
Besides, Lieutenant Colonel Gurren has issued some new orders for our squadron.
Gurren's in Shinjuku?
Oh, that's right. He's reorganizing our troops within the city.
The Lieutenant Colonel is already ahead of us at West Shinjuku in Fifth Street.
He's been fighting the vampire's main forces there.
We need to go back him up.
The main forces.
If we can crush them, then the vampires will be defeated and we'll win this.
They're probably thinking the same thing about us.
If they crush the Moon Demon Company, victory is theirs.
We should get moving.
Mitsu and the others have probably made it to the defensive line by now.
I told you it's not possible.
Our orders are to send everyone we've got to the defensive line.
If the vampires get through there, Shinjuku will fall.
But our troops are going to be wiped out here if we don't help them.
So send in the extermination unit.
They're teenage kids and there's only three of them.
I thought they were supposed to have five members.
The enemy has sent a high-ranking platoon to another...
Hey, you! Wait!
They're going to die.
It's only a matter of time.
All right, fine.
I can spare a few men.
Tell me the location.
What are you saying?
That extermination unit.
Was it the Moon Demon Company?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe.
Why?
Who are you?
We're part of the Moon Demon.
You said there were three of them.
Is it a girl and two guys?
Yeah.
Are you with them or what?
Look, I just need you to tell me where they're fighting.
They're at Shinjuku Central Park.
All right.
We're going to go help them.
Send everyone else to the defensive line.
Got it?
Let's go.
Hey, wait a minute!
You're not thinking clearly.
You can't even be sure that he was talking about our squad.
We can't ignore our orders based on speculation.
We're needed as backup.
That's our top priority.
Even Lieutenant Colonel Gurren will have a hard time going up against the Vampire's strongest forces.
We have to maintain Shinjuku's defensive line.
Gurren is counting on us to be there.
So are the rest of his troops.
We have to maintain each other.
But then we don't need aant zuable.
There's no end to these bloodsuckers.
Mito and I can keep them occupied, while you go after the commander.
When did you get so good at strategizing?
Let's do it!
This fight's finally getting interesting.
It's a shame that Crowley, the 13th progenitor, isn't here.
He would make this a battle truly worthy of the history books.
He's really missing out.
Lachis, Rene, round up our men and take down all the humans except for the one in charge.
Sir, consider it done.
Well, Mika, maybe now I'll finally get a chance to see Cruel Tebysh's favorite servant in action.
You must be very thirsty.
You and I can kill their pompous leader together.
What do you say?
I can do this on my own.
Think so? Then he's all yours.
He will regret coming to attack me.
It will be his undoing.
My sword.
Oh, how intimidating.
I think we're almost there, Hugh.
Yeah.
Thank you.
For coming.
Well, we are a family.
And it's just like Lieutenant Colonel Gurren told us.
We have to protect each other, no matter what.
Idiots.
What?
That's what he would call you.
He probably would.
There it is.
Shinjuku Central Park.
You're reaching.
Behind you.
Damn it.
Dumbass backing us up?
We can't complete a formation without them.
Get ready!
Don't underestimate me!
Kimisaki, watch your back!
Goodbye!
Look, it's you!
Huh?
Don't get distracted on the battlefield, Mitsu.
Where are the rest of the vampires?
They're all dead, genius.
Actually, you just killed the last one of them.
Huh?
Well, damn, you guys.
Looks like you're pretty amazing after all.
You must have forgotten how good I am at killing Vance.
Hey, shouldn't you be backing up Gurren?
What are you talking about?
I heard you were in a tight spot, so I came to make sure you didn't get backed into a corner.
You didn't need to do that.
Besides, we said we'd meet you at the defensive line.
That was your plan.
Sure, that was the plan.
But I just thought...
What, that we would fail?
Well, did you honestly think we didn't have the strength and training to take down an enemy platoon?
You've gotta learn to trust your family.
You're right.
My bad.
Yeah, well, don't go making the same mistake in the future.
Okay?
Sorry, but if it was to happen again tomorrow, I'd still come running.
You what?
Did you hear anything I just said?
It's not that I don't trust you or think that you're weak.
It's just that I care.
I'd do it tomorrow, the day after, forever.
What was I thinking?
I must have forgotten what a hardcore dumbass you can be.
You shouldn't bother wasting your breath with him, Kamizuki.
You can't fix his brand of stupid.
You're right.
Seems the more we try, the dumber he gets.
Oh, come on, guys.
They're just kidding.
The sun is finally out.
Now that we've cleaned out the park, we should probably catch up with Gurren.
Yeah, you're right.
And we can go as a full squad.
Ready, you?
Hell yeah, let's move.
We're gonna kill every one of those blood-sucking bastards.
Well, well, you're a strong one.
A challenge at last.
Yes, but not one that you will win.
Explode now, Fudomiya O spell.
Letting a curse on your head.
I thought that you'd be faster.
I evaded the blast.
And besides, do you really think old-school spellcraft works on vampires?
Oh, meager.
Just as I expected.
Tremendous power and overconfidence.
If you're not careful, that arrogance will get the rug pulled out from under you.
Do you need a hand?
What are you getting at?
There's no way I'll lose against him.
The rug underneath you.
You see, our enemies never intended to fight us one-on-one.
They've caught on Shigurei.
Kill them.
Yes, sir.
Goshi, the illusionary spell.
Already on it.
And this is checkmate.
Vampire!
There, Mika.
Now you owe me one.
Damn.
It's worse than I thought.
The silver-haired one must be a noble.
He's way too strong.
Remember, Mika.
It's always a mistake to underestimate the livestock.
There's nothing honorable about the way these greedy little bloodbags fight.
Although I guess you know all about that as an ex-human yourself.
Shut up.
Well, we should probably get serious about this.
Let's fight together.
I don't need your help.
I know what their strategy is now.
My sword.
Drink more of my blood.
There's that arrogance again.
It's an unfortunate holdover from your humanity that's going to get you in trouble one day.
Looks like I'll have to take two pills to pull this one off.
Don't risk it, Lieutenant Colonel!
Distraction will get you killed, little girl.
Speak for yourself.
Oh, wow.
Not bad.
Please, put the pills away.
If you die of shock from taking two of them, then you can't lead us.
But if I don't take them, we'll all end up dead.
The clock is ticking.
We have to kill them before the pills' effects wear off.
Are you done talking yet?
I want to get this over with.
Well, aren't you a polite vampire?
Would you let us have a little more time to regroup?
How much more?
It's time for us to take our medicine, so if you could be quiet for 20 seconds or so, we'd...
Well, you can't blame a guy for trying.
And is it just me, or are you a lot faster than before?
I'm not holding anything back from now on.
Holding back on the battlefield?
Sounds like the strategy of a child.
You shouldn't taunt someone stronger than you.
It's not smart!
Damn you.
I guess this is it.
Looks like his backup has arrived.
Go on, Mika.
Put the poor man out of his misery.
Not good.
He's been cornered.
Quick, everyone, take your pill.
We'll save the lieutenant colonel and then retreat.
Let's do this!
Yeah.
This is the end.
Human.
Do it, then.
Torrent!
You damn vampire!
You get away from him right now!
Another reckless human.
What annoying pests.
No way is that.
You?
I need your blood
You will love tonight
赤い紅色
掻き分けたニオンと
こじ開けたリズンが
ただ平行になら
Come and break it down for me
A river will fall
気がない星でも
願いなせず
最低最強はいた
四拍子が
奏でたいとなら
木漏れ日の赤が騒ぐ
次回は
Seraph of the End
お会いしましょう